Haritha B K, Senior Test Engineer

Bengaluru, India, +91 9447175815, harithabk@gmail.com

PROFILE:

Passionate Senior Software Engineer with 4+ years of experince in Trading System/Stock Exchange domain working with Xoriant Solutions. To join a dynamic organization as a Senior Tester Engineer or any and apply my knowledge of Software Testing Life Cylce.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY:

May 2021 -Current

CATS/MTF, Senior Test Engineer

- Involved in testing, debugging, troubleshooting of the application throughout the life cycle
- Revewing the requirements and preparing test scenarios
- Raising bugs
- Defect tracking in JIRA
- Coordinate with developer
- SCRUM framework
- Provide suggestions and inputs
- Provide KT sessions in teams
- Take the complete responsibilities for items assigned
- Give sign off for pre-live deployment

May 2019 – May 2021

Corporate Finance Platform, Associate Software Engineer

- Involved in development
- Revewing the requirements and preparing test scenarios
- Debugged aplication issues and create bug reports for development teams
- Defect tracking in TFS
- Coordinate with developer

SKILLS:

- Core Java
- Web Application testing(UI)
- API testing
- Testcase writing
- Experince working in CI/CD
- FIX logs testing (FIX 4.4, FIX 4.2)
- Integration Testing
- **Testing Tools:**
 - SOAP UI
 - Postman
 - Verifix
 - MQ Tools

- Regression Testing
- Pentest
- Functional Testing
- Worked in Agile Methodology
- Blackbox/Whitebox testing
- Cross Browser testing
- Selenium
- CATT
- Xray
- JIRA, TFS

EDUCATION

Aug 2015- Mar 2018

MCA, St Aloysius College, Mangalore